{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Zài",
      "answer": "在"
    },
    {
      "question": "Guāngpán",
      "answer": "光盘"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīnyuè",
      "answer": "音乐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chángcháng",
      "answer": "常常"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gēn",
      "answer": "跟"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shāngchǎng",
      "answer": "商场"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǒumíng",
      "answer": "有名"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shū",
      "answer": "书"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bàozhǐ",
      "answer": "报纸"
    },
    {
      "question": "Běnzi",
      "answer": "本子"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nà'er",
      "answer": "那儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Liángzhù",
      "answer": "梁祝"
    }

  ]
}
